{
    "subject": "resource/Decoder_(band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Decoder (band) is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884276986122131,
            "question": "Is United States the hometown of Decoder (band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.879361093044281,
            "question": "Is Decoder (band) an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8207618594169617,
            "question": "What country is Decoder (band)'s hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7206539511680603,
            "question": "Where is Decoder (band) from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6813612580299377,
            "question": "Where was Decoder (band) formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6273552775382996,
            "question": "Where are Decoder (band) based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5046110153198242,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Decoder (band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4764508605003357,
            "question": "What is the origin of Decoder (band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4597160518169403,
            "question": "In which nation did Decoder (band) originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3893127143383026,
            "question": "To which country does Decoder (band) belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Decoder (band) is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9220_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which nation did Decoder (band) originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9220_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin of Decoder (band)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9220_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Decoder (band)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9220_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9220_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: There is no information provided about the band \"Decoder\" or its hometown in any of the given documents. The context discusses a podcast called \"Decoder,\" hosted by Nilay Patel, but does not mention anything related to a band named Decoder or its location."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Decoder (in the context provided) refers to a podcast hosted by Nilay Patel from The Verge, not a band.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context discusses a podcast called Decoder hosted by Nilay Patel, not a band.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "there is no information about a band called Decoder. The context provided seems to be related to a podcast called Decoder hosted by Nilay Patel, and other unrelated texts.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context does not mention Decoder as a band, nor does it provide any information about the hometown of Decoder. Instead, Decoder is described as a podcast hosted by Nilay Patel from The Verge, focusing on big ideas and problems.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}